(Sheldon:)Woo-woo.
(Amy:)Did I tell you our lab got
a grant to study addiction?
(Dr. Brian Greene:)No.
Fascinating work.
(Amy:)I recently trained a capuchin
monkey to smoke cigarettes.
(Sheldon:)Have you learned anything?
(Amy:)Yes. He looks much cooler
than the non-smoking monkeys.
(Amy:)Although it's not
much of a contest.
(Amy:)The other monkeys just
sit around and masturbate.
(Sheldon:)If you don't mind, I'd like to stop
listening to you and start talking.
(Amy:)By all means.
(Sheldon:)Howard has announced
his intention
(Sheldon:)to propose marriage
to Bernadette.
(Amy:)I don't understand.
(Amy:)The original piece of gossip
indicated an impending breakup.
(Sheldon:)I know.
(Sheldon:)The group consensus
is that his proposal
(Sheldon:)will be met with an humiliating,
soul-crushing rejection.
(Sheldon:)Everyone was set a-twitter.
(Sheldon:)Although oddly,
no one tweeted.